const questions = [
  {
    question: "Blue",
    color: "green",
    options: ["Yellow", "Red", "Black", "Blue", "Green", "Orange"],
    answer: "Green",
  },
  {
    question: "Red",
    color: "orange",
    options: ["Orange", "Blue", "Black", "Red", "Green", "Yellow"],
    answer: "Orange",
  },
  {
    question: "Orange",
    color: "black",
    options: ["Green", "Orange", "Blue", "Black", "Yellow", "Red"],
    answer: "Black",
  },
  {
    question: "Green",
    color: "yellow",
    options: ["Black", "Yellow", "Green", "Red", "Blue", "Orange"],
    answer: "Yellow",
  },
  {
    question: "Yellow",
    color: "red",
    options: ["Red", "Green", "Blue", "Black", "Orange", "Yellow"],
    answer: "Red",
  },
  {
    question: "Blue",
    color: "black",
    options: ["Orange", "Yellow", "Black", "Blue", "Red", "Green"],
    answer: "Black",
  },
  {
    question: "Red",
    color: "green",
    options: ["Yellow", "Green", "Orange", "Red", "Blue", "Black"],
    answer: "Green",
  },
  {
    question: "Blue",
    color: "yellow",
    options: ["Yellow", "Blue", "Black", "Red", "Green", "Orange"],
    answer: "Yellow",
  },
  {
    question: "Orange",
    color: "blue",
    options: ["Blue", "Orange", "Green", "Black", "Yellow", "Red"],
    answer: "Blue",
  },
  {
    question: "Black",
    color: "green",
    options: ["Red", "Black", "Green", "Blue", "Yellow", "Orange"],
    answer: "Green",
  },
];
